Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXI is arranged in 253 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXI. SYSTEM BOARDS
  - Sub-Series 250-0. System Boards
    - General, 1944-1946 (Box 166, Folder 6)
      October 1944-May 1946.
    - General, 1944 (Box 166, Folder 7)
      January 1944-September 1944.
    - General, 1943 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - General, 1942 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - General, 1940-1941 (Box 166, Folder 10)
      October 1940-December 1941.
    - General, 1940 (Box 167, Folder 1)
      January 1940-September 1940.
    - General, 1938-1939 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - General, 1934 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - General, 1932 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - General, 1933-1937 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - General, 1930 (Box 167, Folder 6)
      October 1930-November 1930.
    - General, 1929 (Box 167, Folder 7)
      September 1929-December 1929.
    - General, 1921-1929 (Box 167, Folder 8)
      1921-August 1929.
    - General, 1963-1968 (Box 167, Folder 9)
      January 1963-August 1968.
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 167, Folder 10)
      May 1960-December 1962.
    - General, 1956-1960 (Box 167, Folder 11)
      August 1956-April 1960.
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 168, Folder 1)
      1955-July 1956.
    - General, 1951-1954 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      August 1951-54.
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 168, Folder 3)
      August 1950-July 1951.
    - General, 1948-1950 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      June 1948-July 1950.
    - General, 1946-1948 (Box 168, Folder 5)
      June 1946-May 1948.
  - Sub-Series 250-1. System Boards. Atlantic Coast Line
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 168, Folder 7)
      July 1960-62.
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1960 (Box 168, Folder 8)
      July 1957-June 1960.
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      July 1955-June 1957.
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1955 (Box 168, Folder 10)
      April 1953-June 1955.
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 168, Folder 11)
      August 1951-March 1953.
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1952 (Box 168, Folder 12)
      Subject: "Cooperative Board of the Standard Railway Labor Organizations"
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1951 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      1949-July 1951.
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1948 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1944 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1940 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      Subject: "Appeal E.J. Parker, Protesting the Eligibility of Sister Susan Jennette"
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1938 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1924 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-2. System Boards. Illinois Central
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      April 1959-62.
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1959 (Box 169, Folder 6)
      1956-March 1959.
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1955 (Box 169, Folder 7)
      Subject: "Controversy over the election of Division Chairmen for the Memphis Terminal and Memphis Division"
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1955 (Box 169, Folder 8)
      April 1954-55.
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1954 (Box 169, Folder 9)
      1949-March 1954.
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1948 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1947 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Illinois Central System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1943 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 250-3. System Boards. Lehigh Valley
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1961 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      September 26, 1959-June 1961.
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1959 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      1954-September 25, 1959.
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      April 1958-59. Lodges Nos. 930-1109
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1949 (Box 170, Folder 4)
      Subject: "Transfer of clerical employees in the offices of the Auditor of Revenues and the Freight Claim Agent from Philadelphia to Bethlehem and New York. Correspondence pertaining to taking of strike ballot."
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1953 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1943 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 250-4. System Boards. Delaware and Hudson
    - Delaware and Hudson Board of Adjustment, 1957-1962 (Box 170, Folder 7)
      September 21, 1957-62.
    - Delaware and Hudson Board of Adjustment, 1952-1957 (Box 170, Folder 8)
      1952-September 20, 1957.
    - Delaware and Hudson Board of Adjustment, 1939-1951 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 250-5. System Boards. Charleston and Western Carolina Railway
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1961 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-6. System Boards. Cincinnati, Indianapolis, and Western Railway
    - Cincinnati, Indianapolis, and Western Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1926 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-8. System Boards. Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1961 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Delaware, Lackawanna, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1924 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 250-9. System Boards. Louisiana and Arkansas
    - Louisiana and Arkansas System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1932 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 250-10. System Boards. Pittsburgh and Shawmut
    - Pittsburgh and Shawmut System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 250-12. System Boards. Michigan Central System
    - Michigan Central System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Michigan Central System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1958 (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - Michigan Central System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Michigan Central System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1950 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Michigan Central System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1932 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-13. System Boards. Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1966-1969 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      Dissolved, effective July 1, 1969
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1952-1955 (Box 171, Folder 8)
      March 1952-55. Dissolved, effective July 1, 1969
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1949-1952 (Box 171, Folder 9)
      1949-February 1952. Dissolved, effective July 1, 1969
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1934-1948 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Central of Georgia, Savannah and Atlanta, Macon Terminal, Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, Georgia and Florida, Atlanta and West Point, Western Railway of Alabama, Atlanta Joint Terminals, Georgia, Augusta Union Station Board of Adjustment, 1921-1925 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-14. System Boards. Louisville and Nashville
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      July 1957-59.
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      1954-June 1957.
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      May 1951-53.
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1951 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      September 1950-April 1951.
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1950 (Box 172, Folder 5)
      1947-August 1950.
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1946 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 172, Folder 7)
      1939 June 27. Subject: "Minutes of the Twenty-Third Meeting of the Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment"
    - Louisville and Nashville System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1932 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-15. System Boards. Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 172, Folder 9)
      May 19, 1965-December 1965.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1964-1965 (Box 172, Folder 10)
      1964-May 18, 1965.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 172, Folder 12)
      July 1961-62.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1961 (Box 172, Folder 13)
      1960-June 1961.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 173, Folder 1)
      August 16, 1957-59.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1957 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      August 1956-August 15, 1957.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1956 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      April 1954-July 1956.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      1951-March 1954.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1950 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      August 1949-50.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1949 (Box 173, Folder 6)
      February 1948-July 1949.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1946 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      July 19, 1945-January 1946.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1945 (Box 173, Folder 8)
      1944-July 18, 1945.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1943 (Box 173, Folder 9)
      April 1941-43.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1941 (Box 173, Folder 10)
      August 1939-March 1941.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1939 (Box 173, Folder 11)
      1927-July 1939.
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1926 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1921 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-16. System Boards. Lake Erie and Western Railroad
    - Lake Erie and Western Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1925 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-17-0. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment
    - General, 1921-1929 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-17-1. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Allegheny District
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      February 1960-62.
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, 1954-1960 (Box 174, Folder 7)
      May 1954-January 1960.
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      February 1953-April 1954.
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, 1950-1953 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      1950-January 1953.
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, 1930-1949 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, 1921-1929 (Box 174, Folder 11)
      October 1921-January 1929.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-2. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Texas and Louisiana District
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment: Texas Department (Subject: "Legal Department File Re: Brevard Simmons"), 1951-1952 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment: Texas Department, 1954-1962 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 174, Folder 14)
      October 1951-53.
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1952 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      Subject: Appeal of Miss Brevard Simmons
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1952 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1952 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, 1950-1951 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment: Texas Department, 1948-1951 (Box 175, Folder 5)
      December 4, 1948-September 1951.
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment: Texas Department, 1946-1948 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      September 1946-December 3, 1948.
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment: Texas Department, 1945-1946 (Box 175, Folder 7)
      1945-August 1946.
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment: Texas Department, 1930-1944 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment: Texas Department, 1922-1929 (Box 175, Folder 9)
      October 1922-December 1929.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-3. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Trans-Missouri District
    - Trans-Missouri District Board of Adjustment, 1932-1961 (Box 175, Folder 10)
      1932-December 1961.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-4. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Chicago and Western Lakes District
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 175, Folder 11)
      1963-January 18, 1965.
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      October 1961-62.
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1961 (Box 176, Folder 2)
      1958-September 1961.
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1953-1957 (Box 176, Folder 3)
      July 1953-57.
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 176, Folder 4)
      November 1951-June 1953.
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1951 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      January-October 1951.
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1948-1950 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1941-1947 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1929-1940 (Box 176, Folder 8)
      September 1929-40.
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1922-1929 (Box 176, Folder 9)
      December 1922-August 1929.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-5. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Kansas-Oklahoma Midwest Division District
    - Kansas-Oklahoma Midwest Division District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Kansas-Oklahoma Midwest Division District Board of Adjustment, 1922-1957 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-17-6. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. South Atlantic Department District
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1957 (Box 177, Folder 2)
      August 1951-57.
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, 1935-1951 (Box 177, Folder 3)
      1935-July 1951.
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, 1933-1934 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, 1921-1932 (Box 177, Folder 5)
      May 1921-32.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-7. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Empire District
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 177, Folder 6)
      June 25, 1960-62.
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 177, Folder 7)
      Subjects: Salary, Terminal Allowance, Railroad Retirement Tax, Staff Retirement Tax
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1955-1960 (Box 177, Folder 8)
      August 1955-June 24, 1960.
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1952-1955 (Box 177, Folder 9)
      1952-July 1955.
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1950-1951 (Box 177, Folder 10)
      April 1950-51.
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1944-1950 (Box 177, Folder 11)
      1944-March 1950.
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1930-1943 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1923-1929 (Box 177, Folder 13)
      April 1923-December 1929.
    - Empire District Board of Adjustment, 1946 (Box 177, Folder 14)
      1946 June 22. Subject: Minutes of Special Meeting on By-Laws
  - Sub-Series 250-17-8. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Central Pacific District
    - Central Pacific District Board of Adjustment, 1931-1962 (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Central Pacific District Board of Adjustment, 1922-1929 (Box 177, Folder 16)
      August 1922-March 1929.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-9. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Northern District
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1961 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, 1953-1957 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, 1945-1952 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, 1950-1957 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      Subject: Shortage A.R. Fries and Loan
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, 1930-1944 (Box 178, Folder 5)
      April 1930-44.
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, 1929-1930 (Box 178, Folder 6)
      1929-March 1930.
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, 1926-1928 (Box 178, Folder 7)
      November 1926-28.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-10. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Gulf Department District
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 178, Folder 9)
      October 1958-62.
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1954-1958 (Box 178, Folder 10)
      1954-September 1958.
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 178, Folder 11)
      September 1951-53.
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1939-1951 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      1939-August 1951.
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1930-1938 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1941 (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Subject: Quarterly Reports
    - Gulf Department District Board of Adjustment, 1921-1929 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      May 1921-29.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-11. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 179, Folder 6)
      July 1956-58.
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1956 (Box 179, Folder 7)
      1958-June 1956.
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1952 (Box 179, Folder 8)
      July 1951-52.
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1945-1951 (Box 179, Folder 9)
      1945-June 1951.
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1935-1944 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1939-1940 (Box 179, Folder 11)
      Subject: Charges against A. Lennon, R.L. McHenry
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1936-1940 (Box 179, Folder 12)
      Subject: Special Investigating Committee
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1940 (Box 179, Folder 13)
      April 28-29, 1940. Subject: Second Quadrennial Meeting
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1936 (Box 179, Folder 14)
      1936 April 16. Subject: First Quadrennial Meeting
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1932-1934 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Ohio Valley and Eastern Lakes District Board of Adjustment, 1922-1929 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      July 1922-September 1929.
  - Sub-Series 250-17-12. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. New England District
    - New England District Board of Adjustment, 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 3)
      July 1956-61.
    - New England District Board of Adjustment, 1954-1956 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      1954-June 1956.
    - New England District Board of Adjustment, 1950-1953 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      June 1950-53.
    - New England District Board of Adjustment, 1930-1950 (Box 180, Folder 6)
      1930-May 1950.
    - New England District Board of Adjustment, 1921-1928 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      May 1921-28.